export const questionData = [
    {
        question: 'Which event is often considered the spark that ignited World War I?',
        Options: [
            ' The sinking of the Lusitania',
            ' The assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand',
            ' The invasion of Belgium',
            ' The Zimmermann Telegram'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        marked: -1, // -1 means not selected
    },
    {
        question: 'Which countries were part of the Triple Entente?',
        Options: [
            ' Germany, Austria-Hungary, Italy',
            ' France, Russia, United Kingdom',
            ' United States, Italy, Japan',
            ' Ottoman Empire, Bulgaria, Germany'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        marked: -1,
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the primary strategy of trench warfare?',
        Options: [
            ' Quick, mobile attacks',
            ' Naval blockades',
            ' Digging defensive trenches and holding positions',
            ' Aerial bombings'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        question: 'Which battle is considered one of the bloodiest battles of World War I?',
        Options: [
            ' Battle of Verdun',
            ' Battle of the Bulge',
            ' Battle of Stalingrad',
            ' Battle of Midway'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        question: 'What was the main purpose of the Zimmermann Telegram?',
        Options: [
            ' To propose a military alliance between Germany and Mexico',
            ' To declare war on France',
            ' To announce a ceasefire',
            ' To initiate peace talks with Russia'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        marked: -1,
    },
    {
        question: 'Which treaty ended World War I?',
        Options: [
            ' Treaty of Versailles',
            ' Treaty of Paris',
            ' Treaty of Ghent',
            ' Treaty of Tordesillas'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 1,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        question: 'Which country was NOT a member of the Central Powers?',
        Options: [
            ' Germany',
            ' Austria-Hungary',
            ' Bulgaria',
            ' Japan'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 4,
        marked: -1,

    },
    {
        question: 'What new type of warfare was introduced during World War I?',
        Options: [
            ' Guerrilla warfare',
            ' Chemical warfare',
            ' Cyber warfare',
            ' Nuclear warfare'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        marked: -1,
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the main reason for the United States entering World War I?',
        Options: [
            ' The assassination of Archduke Franz Ferdinand',
            ' The invasion of Belgium',
            ' The sinking of the Lusitania and the Zimmermann Telegram',
            ' The Russian Revolution'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 3,
        marked: -1,
    },
    {
        question: 'What was the outcome of the Treaty of Versailles for Germany?',
        Options: [
            ' Germany gained new territories',
            ' Germany was forced to pay reparations and accept blame for the war',
            ' Germany formed a new alliance with Austria-Hungary',
            ' Germany remained largely unaffected'
        ],
        correctAnswer: 2,
        marked: -1,
    },

]